Narrator: Part 4
Alice: I think he’s Nadine’s hair stylist.
He works inside, other people help him…
George: But he doesn’t work on weekends.
Hair stylists work on Saturdays…
Alice: Not all hair stylists.
Charlie: He isn’t a chef, I’m sure.
Restaurants are full on weekends.
And James says he cooks French food, but his specialty is spaghetti carbonara.
That’s Italian!
I think he’s a hair stylist, too.
George: But Nadine says they are friends,
and then she says, “I don’t think he has children.”
She doesn’t know. I think that’s strange.
I think he’s Tyler’s dentist.
He has special qualifications,
and remember, “People don’t always like me.”
Nobody likes dentists.
Alice: We need to agree.
George: I’m sure he’s a dentist.
Alice and Charlie: No, definitely a hair stylist.
Host: Your time’s up, Team B.
So, what’s Mike’s job?
Alice: We think he’s a hair stylist.
Host: Mike, what do you do?
Mike: I’m Tyler’s dentist.
Host: Yes, Mike is Tyler’s dentist.
He says nobody likes dentists, but we like you, Mike!
Thank you very much, everyone!